senderoneclimbing.com 2016-06-15

# Privacy | Sender One Climbing, Yoga, Fitness and Sender City

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We respect your concerns about privacy. This policy is intended to ensure your information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. As we continue to evolve our Web site and incorporate new technologies to improve communication, our policies may change. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis to stay abreast of our most current Privacy Policy practices.

 **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

Currently, Sender One gathers information (such as name, e-mail address and zip code) strictly for contact purposes when users opt to fill out an e-mail submission form to inquire about our company and about membership. In some cases we ask for other optional information including additional contact information and certain demographic information (such as phone number and gender).

 **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

We may use your information to communicate special offers, promotions and information about our company to you via email. If you do not wish to receive these emails you will have the option to opt out of future mailings (see the section below). We may also use your information to compile usage statistics and other data regarding the use of the Web site services. We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, outside of the limited circumstances referenced in the paragraph immediately below. We may, however, share with partners aggregated statistical data that includes users’ demographic information but does not identify them. We reserve the right to provide any and all such aggregated and non-individually identifiable data to third parties.

 **HOW DO WE USE YOUR EMAIL INFORMATION?**

We respect your concerns about privacy. We collect email information to provide a more personalized and relevant experience. If you give us your email address on the home page, when you inquire about membership or sign up, we will send you emails about exclusive offers and news at Sender One. If you have previously opted out of receiving emails from us, providing updated information will act as an ‘opt back-in’.

If you want to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, simply click on the unsubscribe link located on the bottom of all of our emails. Although we strive to update our email list as frequently as possible, you might receive another contact before we are able to remove you. Please note that you will continue to receive Member Services related communications as it pertains to your member account. Sender One may use any of your contact information held on file (including Email, Mailing, Phone & Fax) to communicate with you in relation to day to day administrative activities, such as freeze requests, online purchases and important service alerts. Sender One never sells or rents your name, e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information to third-parties.

 **WE ONLY SHARE USER INFORMATION IN THE WAYS DESCRIBED BELOW:**

Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include creating and maintaining our Web site, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

Protection of Sender One Climbing, LLC: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is necessary to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Sender One Climbing, LLC., our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

 **HOW DO WE PROTECT CHILDREN ON OUR WEB SITE?**

We are committed to making a safe environment for children on our site. When we collect information for membership inquiry purposes, users are informed they must be at least 18 years of age or have parental consent to provide personally identifying information to us. We encourage parents to monitor children’s Internet use to keep them safe while navigating Senderoneclimbing.com and all other areas of the Internet.

 **DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY TO EXTERNAL LINKS FOUND ON THIS WEB SITE?**

While this site may contain links to other sites, please note that when you click on one of these links, you are ‘clicking’ away from senderoneclimbing.com to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **HOW CAN YOU CONTACT SENDER ONE CLIMBING?**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, other areas of our Web site or our clubs, please [contact us](mailto:info@senderoneclimbing.com). Your feedback is always welcome and appreciated
